HOW TO CONVERT TO MICROSOFT WORD FORMAT:

1. Open Microsoft Word
2. Click File > Open
3. Navigate to this folder: J:\EIP Project\Sem-6\Project - 3\New\Pro mood tracking\Pro mood tracking 1\mood-tracker 1\For EIP
4. Select the file: Pro_Mood_Tracker_Report.txt
   (You may need to change the file type filter to "All Files" or "Text Files")
5. Word will automatically open and convert the file
6. Apply formatting as needed:
   - Add proper heading styles
   - Adjust table formatting
   - Ensure diagrams are properly aligned (use a monospaced font like Courier New for diagrams)
7. Save the file as a .docx document using File > Save As
8. Choose "Word Document (.docx)" as the file type

The ASCII art diagrams should preserve their structure in Word. If any diagrams appear misaligned, select them and change the font to a monospaced font like Courier New, Consolas, or Lucida Console.

For better results, consider installing Pandoc (https://pandoc.org/installing.html) and converting directly with:
pandoc "Pro_Mood_Tracker_Report.md" -o "Pro_Mood_Tracker_Report.docx"
